<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on Fleming Systems LLC</title>
    <link>https://fleming.systems/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on Fleming Systems LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 14:10:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fleming.systems/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3cx - My new favorite Phone System</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/3cx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 14:10:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/3cx/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a up-to-date Phone System? I work with a Mitel phone system day in and day out, and if it were up to me we would get rid of it as soon as possible. It is very outdated and due to all the conditions of working today (COVID) it sorely lacks in the ability to provide simple remote worker support.
With the need for a replacement looming, I have been looking into replacement phone systems for a year or so now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advertising Myself</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 20:43:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/advertising/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! What brought you here? Was it Google?! Let&amp;rsquo;s hope so since apparently how google ads work is pay to click! I hope you even send me an email or give me a call via the contact page! I offer free 30 minute consultation over Microsoft Teams or a simple phone call. Thanks COVID!
Here are a few things I would ask during that consultation:
 Are you looking to complete a project or for managed services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Week</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/long-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 23:07:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/long-week/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long week, but a good one I&amp;rsquo;ve spend a day rewriting a lot of my old powershell scripts and what I call functionized them, as they were honestly an awful mess to read. I have a script that pulls a report from ADP on a daily basis an updates Active Directory accordingly. Maybe one day I will divulge it, as it is to this day my most useful script; it is essentially responsible for keeping all employee contact and organizational information correct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ansible First Steps</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/ansible-firststeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 17:33:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/ansible-firststeps/</guid>
      <description>Quick little blurb for today, but I was able to create my first ansible playbook and in scale (my small environment of 4 linux VMs) update all my servers via apt! I have ansible running on MacOS which made the various guide online of how to get it up and running a little off, but I was able to figure it out!
Biggest ah ha moment for me was that on MacOS the ansible directory (installed via brew) was in my home directory &amp;ldquo;/home/tyler/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure App Service, Web Apps, and Containers</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/azureappsvc-webapp-containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 21:17:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/azureappsvc-webapp-containers/</guid>
      <description>Today my goal was to use docker + Azure to get a web app deployed to Microsoft Azure&amp;rsquo;s web apps. After about 2 hours and some reading I was able to get through it!
It should also be noted that before today I have briefly messed with Docker containers in the past but hadn&amp;rsquo;t quite understood the power of containers. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to report that I have become a fan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Out</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/starting-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 13:26:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/starting-out/</guid>
      <description>Starting out with Fleming Systems I had never really considered starting a business of my own&amp;hellip; granted this is a company of me, myself, and I. But I have learned quite a bit since I first started two weeks ago, to include legally and technically.
  Legally, there are a few things I had to do.
 I learned how to form my own LLC and register it with the state of Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>