<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on Fleming Systems LLC</title>
    <link>https://fleming.systems/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on Fleming Systems LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 17:33:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fleming.systems/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ansible First Steps</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/ansible-firststeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 17:33:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/ansible-firststeps/</guid>
      <description>Quick little blurb for today, but I was able to create my first ansible playbook and in scale (my small environment of 4 linux VMs) update all my servers via apt! I have ansible running on MacOS which made the various guide online of how to get it up and running a little off, but I was able to figure it out!
Biggest ah ha moment for me was that on MacOS the ansible directory (installed via brew) was in my home directory &amp;ldquo;/home/tyler/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure App Service, Web Apps, and Containers</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/azureappsvc-webapp-containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 21:17:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/azureappsvc-webapp-containers/</guid>
      <description>Today my goal was to use docker + Azure to get a web app deployed to Microsoft Azure&amp;rsquo;s web apps. After about 2 hours and some reading I was able to get through it!
It should also be noted that before today I have briefly messed with Docker containers in the past but hadn&amp;rsquo;t quite understood the power of containers. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to report that I have become a fan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Out</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/starting-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 13:26:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/starting-out/</guid>
      <description>Starting out with Fleming Systems I had never really considered starting a business of my own&amp;hellip; granted this is a company of me, myself, and I. But I have learned quite a bit since I first started two weeks ago, to include legally and technically.
  Legally, there are a few things I had to do.
 I learned how to form my own LLC and register it with the state of Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>