<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Fleming Systems LLC</title>
    <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Fleming Systems LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 13:29:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fleming.systems/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Disabling Self-Service Purchasing</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/disabling-selfservicepurchasing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 13:29:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/disabling-selfservicepurchasing/</guid>
      <description>Just another way for Microsoft to get more money, rediculous Microsoft will be releasing the &amp;ldquo;feature&amp;rdquo; soon that will allow individual users to purchase certain licensing SKUs themselves through their work accounts. When they attempt to purchase these licenses it will ask for their credit card information, so it won&amp;rsquo;t add a bill to your corporate Microsoft invoice but instead allows the potential for unwanted licenses being purchased.
There are a lot of reason why this could be an issue, but just to name a few:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3cx - My new favorite Phone System</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/3cx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 14:10:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/3cx/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a up-to-date Phone System? I work with a Mitel phone system day in and day out, and if it were up to me we would get rid of it as soon as possible. It is very outdated and due to all the conditions of working today (COVID) it sorely lacks in the ability to provide simple remote worker support.
With the need for a replacement looming, I have been looking into replacement phone systems for a year or so now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 Overview</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/microsoft-365/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 10:04:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/microsoft-365/</guid>
      <description>What is Microsoft 365? This is a very high level overview of the different levels of licensing SKUs offered within Microsoft 365. Office 365 is Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s SaaS solution for their cloud services. Microsoft has recently rebranded to Microsoft 365 as well, leading to more confusion when it comes to Licensing SKUs. There are many products that belong within Microsoft 365, but I will list the main few that I have worked with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advertising Myself</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 20:43:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/advertising/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! What brought you here? Was it Google?! Let&amp;rsquo;s hope so since apparently how google ads work is pay to click! I hope you even send me an email or give me a call via the contact page! I offer free 30 minute consultation over Microsoft Teams or a simple phone call. Thanks COVID!
Here are a few things I would ask during that consultation:
 Are you looking to complete a project or for managed services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Week</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/long-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 23:07:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/long-week/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long week, but a good one I&amp;rsquo;ve spend a day rewriting a lot of my old powershell scripts and what I call functionized them, as they were honestly an awful mess to read. I have a script that pulls a report from ADP on a daily basis an updates Active Directory accordingly. Maybe one day I will divulge it, as it is to this day my most useful script; it is essentially responsible for keeping all employee contact and organizational information correct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ansible First Steps</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/ansible-firststeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 17:33:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/ansible-firststeps/</guid>
      <description>Quick little blurb for today, but I was able to create my first ansible playbook and in scale (my small environment of 4 linux VMs) update all my servers via apt! I have ansible running on MacOS which made the various guide online of how to get it up and running a little off, but I was able to figure it out!
Biggest ah ha moment for me was that on MacOS the ansible directory (installed via brew) was in my home directory &amp;ldquo;/home/tyler/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying out MacOS</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/tryingoutmacos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 21:23:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/tryingoutmacos/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s wrong with me! I finally caved and bought a macbook pro 13&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to try out Mac OS for the longest time and I figured the responsible thing to do with starting the company was to keep everything related to Fleming Systems physically separated from everything else. It&amp;rsquo;s on it&amp;rsquo;s trial run, you get 14 days to return Apple products so I got some time to learn it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure App Service, Web Apps, and Containers</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/azureappsvc-webapp-containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 21:17:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/azureappsvc-webapp-containers/</guid>
      <description>Today my goal was to use docker + Azure to get a web app deployed to Microsoft Azure&amp;rsquo;s web apps. After about 2 hours and some reading I was able to get through it!
It should also be noted that before today I have briefly messed with Docker containers in the past but hadn&amp;rsquo;t quite understood the power of containers. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to report that I have become a fan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Out</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/starting-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 13:26:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/starting-out/</guid>
      <description>Starting out with Fleming Systems I had never really considered starting a business of my own&amp;hellip; granted this is a company of me, myself, and I. But I have learned quite a bit since I first started two weeks ago, to include legally and technically.
  Legally, there are a few things I had to do.
 I learned how to form my own LLC and register it with the state of Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Myself Relevant</title>
      <link>https://fleming.systems/blog/keeping-myself-relevant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 12:44:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fleming.systems/blog/keeping-myself-relevant/</guid>
      <description>How does one do it? With everything technology today, how does one keep themselves relevant with all the information out there! How do you know what you want to spend time reading on, where do you find this information? My answer? I don&amp;rsquo;t! I like to read up on anything related to technology, but I am constantly finding myself having to google information whenever I work on something, be it the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve done it or the 100th!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>